#### **CASEY ROBISON**

### 97 Buell St. Apt. 1, Burlington, VT, 05401 | (206) 612-3605 | mrcaseyrobison@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Career bartender with extensive experience in high volume restaurants and intimate craft cocktail bars. Strives to exceed every guest expectation and provide them with the best experience possible. Brings to the table a deep passion for training and mentoring young bartenders. Recently relocated to Burlington and excited to experience all the wonderful restaurant scene has to offer.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### The Doctor's Office, Seattle, WA

**2021—September 2022** 

Bartender

- Worked as part of a small bar team that was ranked top 10 spirits selection in the world.
- Collaborated on menu program, design, and logistic execution.
- Managed the reservation system and guest communications.

#### Pernod Ricard, Seattle, WA

2018 - 2020

Key Account Manager, New Brand Ventures Portfolio

- Responsible for managing 16 brands across 150 accounts in the greater Seattle area.
- Exceeded KPI's on every brand throughout my term of employment.
- Developed and maintained relationships with buyers across every account.
- Provided expert consultation and training for brands within my portfolio.
- Found new ways of reaching consumers through events, outreach, and social media.

### Heavy Restaurant Group, Seattle, WA

Beverage Program Director

2011 - 2018

- Promoted to corporate management team and was given oversight of financial and operational results of bar programs at 10 locations.
- Oversaw the opening of six locations in three years. Conceptualized bar programs, established purchasing
  and inventory procedures, developed training materials, hired and trained bar teams and managers, all
  while on strict opening deadlines.
- Utilized knowledge of industry culture and consumer trends to drive menu development, staff education, pricing, and inventory control.
- Proudly served as a mentor to new managers and staff to foster future industry leaders.

Bar Manager

2008 - 2011

- Collaborated with management team to open two 150+ seat restaurants focusing on Mexican cuisine, Latin-inspired craft cocktails, and agave spirits.
- Created and executed innovative bar programs with high volume sales, earning praise for spirits and cocktail selection.
- Responsible for weekly purchasing and inventory at both locations.

### **EDUCATION**

### University of Washington, Bachelor of Arts, History

2022

• GPA 3.92 | Dean's List every quarter

## PROFFESIONAL EDUCATION

BAR 5 Day Certified 2019
Scotch Whisky Certified – Level 1, The Whisky Council 2020

#### **COMMUNITY INVOLVMENT**

## "Community Cocktails" Covid-19 Relief Fundraiser

2020

Collected 150 cocktail recipes from bartenders across Washington, edited and compiled them into a digital cocktail book, helping fundraise \$50,000 for Seattle's hospitality industry workers.

# Northwest Immigrants' Rights Project Fundraiser

2017

Conceptualized and organized a city-wide fundraiser, bringing together over 50 restaurants and bars and raising \$30,000 for the Northwest Immigrants' Rights Project.

# Remy-Cointreau Collectif 1806 Conference

2017

• Featured panelist for industry discussion on bar professionalism and management.

### **United States Bartenders Guild**

2011

- Founding member of the USBG-WA, with over 500 active members presently.
- Served as Vice President from 2011 to 2015.

#### REFERENCES

**Dr. Matthew Powell,** The Doctor's Office, Owner – (707) 580-8779 Keith Waldbauer, The Doctor's Office, Bar Manager – (206) 437-6361 Amanda Barker, SGWS, Vice-President, ALD, Direct Supervisor – (206) 817-8334 Cameron George, Ardbeg National Ambassador, Colleague – (206) 307-6901